/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data5_4', {
    title: '5.4 Prime Factorization',
    path: '5.4-prime-factorization',
    children: [{
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 10}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{5}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 10}',
                answer: '\\primefac{10}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 18}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\exp{\\input{3}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 18}',
                answer: '\\primefac{18}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 36}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\exp{\\input{2}}{\\input{2}}}{\\sign{·}}{\\exp{\\input{3}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 36}',
                answer: '\\primefac{36}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 50}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\exp{\\input{5}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 50}',
                answer: '\\primefac{50}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 118}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{59}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 118}',
                answer: '\\primefac{118}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 130}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{5}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{13}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 130}',
                answer: '\\primefac{130}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 145}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{5}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{29}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 145}',
                answer: '\\primefac{145}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 294}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{3}}{\\sign{·}}{\\exp{\\input{7}}{\\input{2}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 294}',
                answer: '\\primefac{294}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 171}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\exp{\\input{3}}{\\input{2}}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{19}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 171}',
                answer: '\\primefac{171}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Writing Prime Factorization of Whole Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write the prime factorization of 106}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\input{2}}{\\sign{·}}{\\input{53}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Prime factor 106}',
                answer: '\\primefac{106}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": true
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
